<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="/feed.xslt.xml"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.2.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-03-19T18:55:39+01:00</updated><id>/</id><title type="html">Tonbridge Digital</title><subtitle>Promoting the digital economy in Tonbridge through meetups, discussion and networking</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Launch!</title><link href="/articles/launch/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Launch!" /><published>2017-02-20T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2017-02-20T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>/articles/launch</id><content type="html" xml:base="/articles/launch/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;hello&quot;&gt;Hello&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m Calum and I’ve been living in or near Tonbridge now for over five years and in that time have seen it progress into a much more vibrant town centre with what seems like more, not less, independent businesses, restaurants, shops and cafes opening up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that the population is gradually increasing as younger generations of families and individuals have moved here. I’m keen to see how a strong digital economy in town can help strengthen the local economy of Tonbridge at a time when our economy is experiencing tough challenges and an uncertain future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Previously I ran a small group for web industry professionals however felt we needed to involve a wider audience so started Tonbridge Digital. With this new group I hope to attract businesses and individuals, &lt;em&gt;be they directly involved or not, in selling&lt;/em&gt;, using or promoting with digital-based solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the coming months I’ll be planning what kind of events and social gatherings that can be organised within Tonbridge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contact me directly if you have ideas or would like to help out in whatever way &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:general@tonbridge.digital&quot;&gt;general@tonbridge.digital&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="general" /><summary type="html">Introductory speech ahead of launching Tonbridge Digital</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="{&quot;feature&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;credit&quot;=&gt;nil, &quot;creditlink&quot;=&gt;nil}" /></entry></feed>
